{
    "subject": "resource/George_Herbert_Scott",
    "predicate": "property/airForce",
    "object": "RNAS, RAF",
    "human_readable": "George Herbert Scott was a pilot in RNAS, RAF.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9204879999160767,
            "question": "Did George Herbert Scott fly for the RAF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9203253388404846,
            "question": "Was George Herbert Scott a member of the RNAS?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.822505533695221,
            "question": "In which organizations did George Herbert Scott serve as a pilot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7753176093101501,
            "question": "During what historical period did George Herbert Scott serve as a pilot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.672911524772644,
            "question": "What were the responsibilities of a pilot in the RNAS and RAF?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5790926218032837,
            "question": "What type of aircraft did George Herbert Scott likely fly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4539686143398285,
            "question": "What was George Herbert Scott's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3972163796424866,
            "question": "Were there any notable missions or events associated with George Herbert Scott's piloting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28162071108818054,
            "question": "How did technological advancements during George Herbert Scott's time affect aviation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.049017783254384995,
            "question": "Can you describe the training and qualifications required to become a pilot in the early 20th century?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=George Herbert Scott was a pilot in RNAS, RAF.",
            "html": "dbpedia_730_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did technological advancements during George Herbert Scott's time affect aviation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_730_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable missions or events associated with George Herbert Scott's piloting career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_730_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was George Herbert Scott's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_730_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_730_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents mention Major George Herbert \"Lucky Breeze\" Scott, CBE, AFC, as a British airship pilot and engineer, who served in the RNAS/RAF."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that George Herbert Scott was indeed a pilot in both the Royal Naval Air Service (RNAS) and the Royal Air Force (RAF). Specifically, the document states, \"After serving with the RNAS / RAF in WW1 he went on to Command the airship R34 on its return Atlantic Crossing in 1919 which marked the 1st transatlantic flight by an airship and the 1st east-west transatlantic flight by an aircraft of any kind.\" This information confirms his role as a pilot in both services."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}